Okay, so let's look at the solution.
이제 해결방법을 볼까요
If you said either layout_width or layout_height,
만약 레이아웃_넓이 혹은 높이에 관해,
those wouldn't be bad guesses.
생각했다면 틀린 생각은 아닙니다.
It's really important to choose these values carefully as as they
이는 정말로 조심히 생각하여 선택하여야합니다 왜냐하면
affect the space that your element takes up.
이는 당신이 입력하는 공간에 영향을 미치기 때문이죠.
For example let's talk about layout_width.
예를들어 레이아웃_넓이에 대해 이야기해보겠습니다.
Suppose that I have a text box that says, hi.
예를들어 안녕이라는 텍스트 박스를 입력합니다.
And I set the layout_width to be wrap content.
그리고 저는 화면을_넓게 설정하겠습니다.
By default,
영구설정함으로,
this will just stick that text box into the upper left-hand corner.
이는 텍스트창에 상단 좌측 구석에 보여질 것입니다.
Then, if I use another attribute to push it over to the right,
그리고 다른 설정을 넣어서
the text box will be here.
텍스트 박스는 이곳으로 이동하게됩니다.
If instead,
아니면,
I use match parent, by default, hi will still be in the upper left-hand corner.
저는 영구설정으로 사앋ㄴ 우측 좌측으로 설정합니다.
But if I then try to set an attribute to push it to the right,
하지만, 만약 알맞는 장소에 설정한다면,
it'll try to push this text box to the right.
이는 올바른 장소로 텍스트 박스가 이동할 것입니다.
But it already is as far right as it could be because it's expanding
하지만, 확장으로 인해서 너무 많이 이동했다면,
to match the parent and fill the whole view group.
부모화면과 맞추고 화면 설정 그룹을 채워야합니다.
In the case of using match parent,
부모 화면을 조정하는데 있어서,
we can see that the hi text hasn't actually moved.
우리는 "hi" 문구가 실제로 움직이지 않은 것을 알 수 있습니다.
So one thing that's hopefully clear for this example is that we're going to
그래서 확실히 하기위해, 이 예시에서 우리는
want to set both layout_width and layout_height to wrap content.
두가지 화면 설정_넓이 및 _높이를 대화창을 위해 설정하겠습니다.
So it wraps exactly around the content and
그래서 이는 대화창을 확실히 감싸며
then when you tell the TextView to be either to the right, left, above,
그리고 TextView에 우측, 좌측, 상단 및
below, it'll actually move that text to that location.
아래를 설정하고, 이는 실제로 대화창의 위치를 설정합니다.
Okay, so both layout width and layout height are important.
좋습니다, 이제 넓이와 높이는 정확해졌습니다.
TextStyle is an attribute for bolding or italicizing text, and
TextStyle은 굵게 혹은 이탤릭체 그리고
it really doesn't involve positioning or spacing.
위치 혹은 띄여쓰기에 관여하지 않습니다.
Orientation is an attribute used specifically with linear layouts,
위치는 밑줄이 있는 양식을 사용하고,
to determine whether they are going to be vertical or horizontal.
수평으로 갈지 수직으로 갈지 결정합니다l.
Because we're using a relative layout this also doesn't make any sense.
관련 레이아웃은 말이 안되는 설정이 있기때문입니다.
Layout_weight is really useful for spacing out elements evenly but again,
레이아웃_넓이는 양식을 동등하게 이용하게 하지만,
this is a linear layout attribute.
이는 양식의 기본 사항입니다.
Which leaves us with these attributes.
이 양식을 남기는 것이죠.
All of these attributes have to do with relative layouts.
모든 양식들은 관련 레이아웃들이 있습니다.
Now these attributes layout_to Right Of and layout_below are categorically
이제, 이 양식들이 layout_to Right Of 및 layout_below 로 정렬될 것입니다.
different than the layout_alignParent either Bottom left or right.
layout_alignParent의 아래쪽 혹은 우측과는 다르게 말입니다.
These attributes take two child views and
이 설정은 두가지 자식 화면을 이용하며
position them relative to one another.
다른 쪽과 관련짓게 합니다.
For example, we could say position from Lyla to the right of and
예를들어, 우리는 Lyla 를 우측에 위치하고
below the happy birthday Ben TextView.
아래에 생일축하합니다 Ben TextView을 입력합니다.
Let's see what that would like like.
어떤지 확인해볼까요.
Okay, so if we did that and
만약 이것을 수행했다면
we just looked at the two TextViews, this is the code that we would use.
저희는 두가지TextViews가 있고, 이 코드는 저희가 사용 가능합니다.
With the happy birthday Ben TextView, I've created an ID here.
생일축하합니다 Ben TextView과, 이곳에 작성한ID 입니다.
And then I refer to that ID from the from Lyla TextView with the layout below
이제 ID를 Lyla TextView를 아래 레이아웃을 사용하여 만듭니다.
and layout right of attributes.
그리고 우측 양식을 사용합니다.
Here's a picture of what that actually looks like in the app and unfortunately,
여기 그림에서 앱과 일치하는 것을 찾습니다 하지만,
that didn't really do what we wanted.
저희가 원하는 것이 이곳에 없네요.
The From Lyla view is in fact to the right of
&gt;From Lyla양식은 우측에
the Happy Birthday Ben TextView.
생일축하합니다 Ben TextView를 포함합니다.
And it is also below, but it's not in the lower right-hand corner.
그리고 이 아래에, 우측 하단에 있지 않는 표시가 있습니다.
So these two aren't correct.
즉 두개가 알맞지 않는 것인데요.
Okay, so that leaves us with these three attributes,
이제, 세가지 사항을 남겼습니다,
which will take my TextView and
바로 제 TextView를 가져오고
align them in relation to the Parent, which happens to be the whole screen.
부모 화면에 전체 화면에 보이도록 설정하는 것입니다.
Now I want From Lyla to be down here.
이제 이곳에From Lyla를 적겠습니다.
Which is in the lower right-hand corner of the parent.
부모화면의 하단 우측구석에 표시합니다.
So I'm not going to be using layout_alignParentLeft, so in fact I
그리고 layout_alignParentLeft사용하지 않고 대신에,
will be using layout_alignParentRight and layout_alignParentBottom.
layout_alignParentRight 및 layout_alignParentBottom을 사용합니다.
Let's see how this all comes together in the code.
이제 모든 것이 코드에 함께 포함된 것을 볼 수 있습니다.
Okay, so first things first.
이제 한개씩 하죠.
I'm going to find the From Lyla TextView and iIm going to make sure that
저는From Lyla TextView 찾아서 화면의 넓이와 높이가
the layout width and the layout height are both set to wrap_content otherwise,
정확한지 확인하고 두개 모두 wrap_content인지 확인하며,
even if we position our textview correctly it might not actually move.
비록 위치가 움직일지도 모르지만 말입니다.
Next I'm going to add the additional attributes.
다음에, 추가 설정 항목을 추가할 것입니다.
For the value, I go ahead and put true.
값을 위해서, 저는 참값을 입력할 것입니다.
This is affirming that I want this TextView to be aligned
이는 TextView가 정확하게 부모 화면 우측에 입력되었는지
to the Parent's Right.
확인하는 과정입니다.
The other value I could put here is false, but that would mean
다른 값은 거짓으로 표시하고 이는
that it is false that it aligns to the Parent Right, which is not what I want.
부모화면 우측에 위치하면 표시되게 설정을 합니다.
So now I'm going to type the other attribute to put at the bottom.
이제 저는 다른 설정을 아래쪽에 입력하고자합니다.
And I will also set this to true.
그리고 이 값을 참으로 설정합니다.
All right, so for those of you at home this might be a little bit hard to see
좋습니다, 이제 집에서 보기 조금 어려울 수 있지만
but it seems like we've positioned our view down here correctly.
이는 정확하게 원하는 값을 입력하였습니다.
That said, let's see if it actually shows up correctly on the phone
이것은 실제로 녹색 실행 버튼을 클릭하여 휴대전화에
by pressing the green Run button.
보여지는 것으로 확인할 수 있습니다.
Okay, I select my phone and I click OK.
네, 휴대전화를 클릭하고 네를 클릭합니다.
Okay, awesome.
좋습니다.
So up here I have my Happy Birthday, Ben, and down here, I have From Lyla.
이제 여기에 생일축하 메세지와 Ben 그리고 아래에 Lyla로 부터가 있네요.
And with that,
이것으로,
everything looks like it's pretty much in the correct position.
모든 것이 알맞은 장소에 있다는 것을 확인할 수 있습니다.